https://grahamthompson.com/privacy-policy/

Practice AreasBanking & FinanceCorporate, Commercial & SecuritiesEmployment & LabourImmigration & NaturalizationLitigation & Dispute ResolutionPrivate Clients, Trusts & EstatesProperty & DevelopmentShipping, Admiralty & AviationAbout UsMembershipsPublic ServiceAttorneysCorporate ServicesNews/Legal UpdatesOfficesNassauFreeportLyford CayProvidenciales
Excerpts from a September 2018 interview of Graham Thompson Founder Peter D. Graham by Senior Partner Sean McWeeney, QC.
Privacy Policy
Managing Site Data
Contact information is maintained in our marketing database to advise our audiences of firm news, events and services, as well as for internal statistical analysis. We will protect the confidentiality and security of such information to the fullest extent required and permitted by law. While we may forward contact details to appointed agencies that assist us in processing mailings, we will not provide them to any other party for any other purpose, other than as required by law or in response to an investigation by law enforcement or other government agencies.
When you send us your personal information, GrahamThompson and its affiliates will use your email address and other information to respond to your request and to provide you with information regarding our client services. When you send us a copy of your resume or curriculum vitae, we will use the information contained therein to match you with any relevant opportunity that may arise within GrahamThompson and assess your application. Unless we obtain your permission, we will not use your email address and information for any other purpose.
We do not retain any more of your personal information that we believe is necessary for any of these purposes and we do not retain your personal information for any longer than is reasonably necessary to do so.
As GrahamThompson is an international firm, your personal information may be transferred between our servers and offices. By sending us your personal information you consent to us making any necessary cross border transfers of your personal information.
Our website contains links to other websites for your convenience only. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy policies or the contents of such other websites and we advise you to read the privacy policies of each website you visit which collects personal information.
Collection and Use of Information
We use session cookies to ensure that your computer displays our website effectively and to track anonymously the usage of our website. A session cookie is a small data file which is temporarily stored on your computer’s hard disk or website server and does not collect personal information. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies using your web browser settings. If you choose to not accept cookies from our website, you may not be able to take full advantage of certain of its features or to receive some of the services that it provides.
If at any time you no longer wish to receive information from GrahamThompson and its affiliates you can advise us by return email. GrahamThompson reserves the right not to distribute, or discontinue distributing to, any person.
International Transfers of Information
Any email you send through the website may be routed through the United States or additional jurisdictions other than your home country or The Bahamas. By your use of the website, you expressly consent to the transfer of that information across international borders and you acknowledge that such information may be processed and stored in a country with privacy laws that may differ from those of your own country.
By providing personal information to us through our website you consent to our use of it as set forth in this privacy policy.
Search
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.OkPrivacy policy
